#### Contact

angela\_cohen@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/angela-cohen-mcgaskey-msn-rn-cnml-1b64a8147 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Nursing
Critical Care
Microsoft Office

# Angela Cohen-McGaskey, MSN, RN, CNML

Research Nurse Manager at University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center

Missouri City, Texas

## Summary

Experienced Intensive Care Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the Hospital & Health Care industry. Skilled in Critical Care Nursing, Healthcare Management, Leadership, Microsoft Office, and Nursing. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master of Science in Nursing focused in Executive Nurse Leadership from The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston.

# Experience

University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center Research Nurse Manager January 2018 - Present (2 years 5 months)

The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center UTHealth Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences Critical Care Registered Nurse

Harris Health System
Neurosurgical Intensive Care Nurse
January 2012 - June 2015 (3 years 6 months)
Houston, Texas Area

### Education

The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston

Master of Science in Nursing, Executive Nurse Leadership (2015 - 2017)

The University of Texas at Arlington
Bachelor of Science In Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2012 - 2015)

#### San Jacinto College

Associate of Arts and Sciences - AAS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse  $\cdot$  (2008 - 2010)

#### Houston Community College

Certificate, Licensed Practical/Vocational Nurse Training · (2005 - 2005)